call center healthc care provider
roleplay number one call center
agent and
customer thank you for calling vital
Care Health Solutions my name is Terry
how may I assist you today hello I'm
calling because I have some questions
about my health insurance plan and
coverage of course I'm here to help may
I have your name and policy number
please sure my name is Thomas K Douglas
and my policy number is
hold on I have it here on a piece of
paper it's VC 25 3-7 1
07 thank you Mr Douglas what questions
do you have regarding your health
insurance plan and coverage well first
of all I'm not sure about the coverage
for preventive care can you explain
what's included in my plan certainly I'd
be happy to answer that with your plan
you have comprehensive coverage for
preventive care including vaccinations
screenings and annual
checkups these services are generally
covered at 100% meaning you won't have
to pay any out-of-pocket costs for
them that's great to know secondly I
recently started a new
medication and I'm curious if it's
covered under my prescription drug
benefits I understand the importance of
medication
coverage to provide accurate information
could you please tell me the name of the
medication and the
dosage it's called health aid and I take
the 20 MGR dosage it's one pill per
day thank you for that information let
me check that for you please give me a
few seconds yes I found
it you'll be responsible for a
co-payment of $20 per 30-day Supply when
you fill your prescription at a network
Pharmacy perfect lastly I'm planning on
taking a trip abroad next month will my
health insurance cover International
medical
expenses that's a great question while
your plan does offer some coverage for
emergency medical expenses abroad it's
essential to be aware that coverage may
be
limited I recommend contacting our
travel assistant hotline before your
trip to get more information and
guidance on international
coverage they'll be able to provide
specific details thank you for the
detailed information
I feel much more informed now I recently
got a new job so my insurance policy is
a little different compared to my
previous job I just haven't had time to
work out the
specifics of course sir I completely
understand if you have any more
questions or need further assistance
feel free to reach out to any of our
representatives and we would be happy to
answer your questions or concerns thank
you for that what's your name
again it's Terry
thank you Terry you've been very
helpful it has been my pleasure Mr
Douglas do you have any other questions
at this
time no I think you've answered them all
thanks again you are most welcome have a
wonderful day goodbye
goodbye call center healthc care
provider roleplay number two call center
agent and customer
thank you for calling vital Care Health
Solutions my name is Carson how may I
assist you today hi I have a few
questions about my health insurance
specifically regarding mental health
coverage of course I can most certainly
help you with that could you please
provide your name and policy number sure
my name is Monique Rodriguez and my
policy number is m987
654321 thank you Monique is there
anything in particular you would like to
know well I'm wondering about the
specific mental health services covered
by my plan are therapy sessions and
counseling included in the plan
absolutely Mo'Nique your plan includes
coverage for mental health services
including therapy and counseling
depending on the specifics of the
provider and type of service you may
have a co-payment or co-
insurance I can check your specific
benefits if you provide me with the
names of any mental health professionals
you're considering
that's good to know second question if I
need to see a psychiatrist for
medication management how does that work
with my
insurance that's an important aspect of
mental health care if you need to
consult with a psychiatrist for
medication management it falls under
your Behavioral Health Coverage keep in
mind you may need a referral from your
primary care physician and any
medications prescribed will be subject
to your prescription drug
benefits hm how can I get more
information about which drugs are
covered under my insurance
plan if you do a search on our homepage
there is a list of drugs that are
covered under each plan you can also do
a search for specific drugs to see if
they are
covered got it lastly I've heard about
teleah health options for mental health
services does my plan cover virtual
therapy
sessions yes Monique your plan does
offer coverage for virtual therapy
sessions through tella Health
Services it's a convenient option
especially in in today's digital age the
same cost sharing rules apply but it
provides flexibility for accessing
Mental Health Care from the comfort of
your home thank you for the information
that's really good to know you're
welcome Monique if you have any more
questions or need further clarification
don't hesitate to reach out we're here
to help thank you I think you answered
all my questions excellent is there
anything else I can help you with today
no that should do it for now have
yourself a nice day you too goodbye
goodbye remember to watch our other
roleplay videos
[Music]